rollapp.com 2019-07-07

# rollApp - Privacy Policy

rollApp is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our websites [www.rollApp.com](https://www.rollapp.com/) or [rollMyFile.com](https://rollmyfile.com/) and use our online or other services ("Services"). In this policy we explain how and why we collect your information, what we do with it and what controls you have over our use of it.

From time to time, we add or change functions, features or products to our website or add or change Services. This, as well as our commitment to protecting the privacy of your personal information, may result in periodic changes to this Privacy Policy. Please remember to refer back to this Privacy Policy regularly to review any amendments.

## Information We Collect And How We Use It

We may collect the following types of information:

  * Information you provide — When you sign up for a rollApp Account, we may ask you for personal information. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information.
  * Cookies — When you access rollApp Services, we may send one or more cookies to your computer or other devices. We may use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving search results and ad selection, and tracking user trends, such as how people search. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some rollApp features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.
  * Log information — When you access rollApp Services via a browser, application or other clients, our servers may automatically record certain information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, your interaction with a service, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account.
  * User communications — When you send an email or other communications to rollApp, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. We may use your email address to communicate with you about our services.
  * Third Party Components and Applications — rollApp makes available some third-party components and applications through rollApp Services. The information collected by rollApp when you enable a third party application is processed under this Privacy Policy. Information collected by the third party application/component provider is governed by their privacy policies.
  * Other sites — This Privacy Policy applies to rollApp Services only. We do not exercise control over the sites that use components provided by rollApp, link to rollApp Sites or are linked from rollApp Sites. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

In addition to the above, we may use the information we collect to:

  * Provide, maintain, protect, and improve our services (including advertising services) and develop new services; and
  * Protect the rights or property of rollApp or our users.

We use the information we collect to provide rollApp Services and to facilitate other interactions related to and in support of the providing of rollApp Services. In addition to the above, we use the information for following specific purposes:

  * Providing the service. The main area, where the information about you is used, is providing the rollApp Services. This includes authenticating you upon login, processing payment transactions, communicating with you about your use of the rollApp Services, providing support and overall maintaining and operating the service. When you use different products that comprise rollApp Services, we use information about you to provide you with integrated experience to improve your productivity and increase utility if the services we provide.
  * Research and development. We are constantly working to improve the services we provide, and the information we collect and direct feedback from our users help us identify areas for improvement and further development of our services.
  * Customer support. Collected information can be used to respond to support requests and to provide assistance for technical issues reported by the users and identified by our team.
  * Security. Using the information we collect we monitor, assess and verify accounts and activities in our systems to identify and prevent fraudulent activities and service abuse.
  * Protecting our legitimate business interests and legal rights. We use the information we collected, when required by law or when we believe it is necessary to protect our legal rights and interests. Specifically, in relation to legal claims, compliance, and regulatory requirements.

If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

rollApp processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America and Canada, in the EU countries and in other countries. In some cases, we may process personal information outside of your own country.

The period of retention for the information we collect depends on the nature of information. After that period has expired we will delete or anonymize information we collected. If the deletion is not possible, we will securely store the information until it becomes possible to delete it.

We keep your account information for as long as your account is active. After you account was deleted we retain some of your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes, to enforce our agreements, to support business operations, and to continue to develop and improve our Services.

## Children’s Privacy

rollApp recognizes the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. Our Services are not intended for children under the age of 13. rollApp does not target its Services or its website to children under 13. rollApp does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

## Information Sharing

rollApp only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of rollApp in the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.
  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of rollApp, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If rollApp becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## Logging In To rollApp

rollApp provides its users with the ability to create a new account, or sign-in to an existing account using their Google, Twitter, Facebook or other Open ID credentials. If you choose to use a third party ID to sign in to rollApp, the first time you select this option you may be prompted by the third party service to allow rollApp the privilege of being able to access/post content on/to your third-party service (i.e. Facebook). The third party service may also ask if you want to allow rollApp access to your email address and/or some other information. Accepting these requests allows you to use your third party ID credentials to access rollApp, and also signals your acceptance of rollApp’s Terms of Service. If you choose to revoke these privileges from rollApp, you can do so at any time by accessing the applicable applications settings under your third-party service.

## Information Security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to rollApp employees, contractors, and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution if they fail to meet these obligations.

## Accessing And Updating Personal Information

When you use rollApp Services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Because of the way we maintain certain services after you delete your information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems.

## Notification Of Changes

Due to the Internet's rapidly evolving nature, rollApp may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

_Last updated: 07-07-2018_
